Camila Nascimento

Computer Engineer / Software Developer | Powercoders Participant Hängelenweg 2, 3123 Belp, Switzerland | 22/11/1984 | Residence permit B camila.nascimento@powercoders.org | +41 77 456 63 38

GitHub | Learning Blog | LinkedIn

Languages: English (C1), German (B2), Spanish (A2),

Portuguese (mother tongue)

IT skills: Advance: C#, .NET, SQL

Intermediate: JavaScript

Elementary: HTML, CSS, Java, Angular, Dynamic 365



I am a Computer Engineer with 7 years work experience in the IT industry. I hold a Microsoft Certified Professional Developer (MCPD) certificate and am an experienced user of C#, .Net and SQL. I'm a determined, disciplined and flexible person and am looking for a Software Developer position in a great company.

WORK EXPERIENCE

11/2018 - 09/2020

Branch Manager/Sandwich Artist, Subway, Langenthal/Thun/Bern, Switzerland

- Promoted to manager of Langenthal branch within 3 months of start
- Handled inventory, weekly food orders, team work plan, cashier and ensured diligent control of revenues
- Checked products and restocked items to ensure a sufficient supply throughout the shifts and the week
- Ensured excellent customer service

02/2015 - 05/2016

Administration Manager, Government of District Federal of Brazil, Brasilia, Brazil

- Planned, organized, directed and controlled the sectors: administrative, technological, financial, patrimonial and protocol
- Managed a team of 14 people with very few financial resources
- Elaborated and managed documents and reports

08/2012 - 06/2014

.NET and C# Developer, Emgea (Government public assets company), Brasilia, Brazil

- Developed, implemented and maintained software with .NET, C# and SQL
- Altered process code to correct errors or make system changes using Agile and SCRUM methodologies
- Initiated regular customer surveys to understand clients' needs and experience to continuously improve their satisfaction
- Managed to work in a team with 7 peoples, ensuring the stability of systems in production, handling branches and features



	 Web Developer, Autotrac (Company specialized in equipment development, software and mobile data communication services), Brasilia, Brazil Developed and implemented the company's first e-commerce shop with .NET and C# from scratch within 6 months Webmaster of e-commerce with JavaScript, jQuery, HTML and CSS Handled database with SQL Server Learned und applied the contenting Management with Umbraco CMS Tested under simulated operating conditions
06/2010 — 06/2011	Web Developer Trainee, Clue Design (Web Design Expert Company), Perth, Australia - Learnt to develop, implement and maintain web pages with .NET and C#
EDUCATION	
09/2020 – 12/2020	 Powercoders – Coding Academy for Refugees, Zurich, Switzerland Foundations in HTML, CSS, JavaScript; specialization tracks upcoming Weekly business & social skills training (team work, communication, etc.)
04/2019 — 06//2019	Telc exam training for German certificate B1, Volkhochschule, Bern, Switzerland
08/2016 – 04//2018	German language course, Migros Klubschule, Bern, Switzerland - Completed Level A1 until B2
09/2012 – 07/2014	Specialization in Software Engineering with emphasis on Productivity and Quality, IESB - Brasilia Institute of Higher Education, Brasilia, Brazil
02/2003 – 07/2008	Computer Engineering , IESB - Brasilia Institute of Higher Education, Brasilia, Brazil
CERTIFICATION	
06/2019	Telc German Certificate B1, Telc Institute, Bern, Switzerland
05/2010 – 07/2011	Microsoft Certified Professional Developer , Australia Institute of Commerce + Technology, Perth, Australia

HOBBIES

Pilates, Crossfit, Hiking, Stand Up Paddle and Skiing.

REFERENCES

- Hussam Allaham, Powercoders Industry Lead, hussam.allaham@powercoders.org, +41 77 906 16 27
- Behrang Dezhbakhsh, Franchise owner, Subway, <u>behrangd@me.com</u>, +41 76 344 09 27
- Daniel Leibundgut, Vice Director, T+R AG, <u>daniel-leibundgut@bluewin.ch</u>, +41 795 24 34